{
    "categories": [{
            "name": "Wildlife",
            "questions": [{
                    "question": "What is the fastest type of shark?",
                    "options": ["Great White", "Hammerhead", "Mako", "Tiger"],
                    "answer": "Mako"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the oldest estimated age of a Greenland shark?",
                    "options": ["100", "200", "300", "400"],
                    "answer": "400"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which animal has the largest brain in ratio to its body size?",
                    "options": ["Dolphin", "Elephant", "Human", "Sperm Whale"],
                    "answer": "Sperm Whale"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which animal is known for its exceptional memory?",
                    "options": ["Elephant", "Octopus", "Dog", "Chimpanzee"],
                    "answer": "Elephant"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which animal can hold its breath the longest underwater?",
                    "options": ["Hippo", "Seal", "Turtle", "Whale"],
                    "answer": "Whale"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which animal is the largest mammal on Earth?",
                    "options": ["Elephant", "Giraffe", "Blue Whale", "Gorilla"],
                    "answer": "Blue Whale"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which bird has the largest wingspan?",
                    "options": ["Albatross", "Condor", "Eagle", "Pelican"],
                    "answer": "Albatross"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which bird can fly backward?",
                    "options": ["Hummingbird", "Ostrich", "Penguin", "Kiwi"],
                    "answer": "Hummingbird"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which bird is the symbol of wisdom?",
                    "options": ["Owl", "Eagle", "Peacock", "Swan"],
                    "answer": "Owl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which bird is known for its ability to mimic human speech?",
                    "options": ["Parrot", "Flamingo", "Sparrow", "Crow"],
                    "answer": "Parrot"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "name": "Motorbikes",
            "questions": [{
                    "question": "What is the top speed of the Kawasaki Ninja H2R?",
                    "options": ["200 km/h", "300 km/h", "400 km/h", "500 km/h"],
                    "answer": "400 km/h"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which motorcycle brand holds the record for the most Grand Prix Motorcycle Racing World Championships?",
                    "options": ["Honda", "Yamaha", "Ducati", "Suzuki"],
                    "answer": "Honda"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the engine displacement of the Harley-Davidson Fat Boy?",
                    "options": ["750cc", "1200cc", "1600cc", "1800cc"],
                    "answer": "1800cc"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which motorcycle company introduced the first mass-produced electric motorcycle?",
                    "options": ["Zero Motorcycles", "Harley-Davidson", "BMW Motorrad", "Ducati"],
                    "answer": "Zero Motorcycles"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of a catalytic converter in a motorcycle's exhaust system?",
                    "options": ["Increasing top speed", "Enhancing fuel efficiency", "Reducing emissions", "Improving suspension"],
                    "answer": "Reducing emissions"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which motorcycle race is known as 'The Isle of Man TT'?",
                    "options": ["British Superbike Championship", "MotoGP", "World Superbike Championship", "Tourist Trophy"],
                    "answer": "Tourist Trophy"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the meaning of the abbreviation 'ABS' in relation to motorcycles?",
                    "options": ["Anti-Brake Skid", "Automatic Braking System", "Advanced Bike Suspension", "Anti-Lock Braking System"],
                    "answer": "Anti-Lock Braking System"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which motorcycle brand is famous for its off-road bikes, such as the CRF series?",
                    "options": ["Suzuki", "KTM", "Kawasaki", "Triumph"],
                    "answer": "Honda"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of a quickshifter in a motorcycle?",
                    "options": ["To adjust the suspension settings", "To change gears without using the clutch", "To control the throttle response", "To activate the traction control system"],
                    "answer": "To change gears without using the clutch"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which motorcycle company produces the 'Ducati Panigale V4' superbike?",
                    "options": ["Ducati", "Yamaha", "Kawasaki", "Honda"],
                    "answer": "Ducati"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}
